Sam Altman.
Sam, of course, the headlines right now,
Elon Musk making a bid apparently for
Openai.
Your response?
You're turning him down for 97 billion.
I mean, look over here.
It's not for sale.
The open admission is not for sale.
Ellen tries all sorts of things for a
long time.
This is the late, you know, this week's
episode.
You take it seriously.
It's all.
What do you think he's trying to drive
out with this?
I think he's probably just trying to
slow us down.
He obviously is a competitor.
It's, you know, he's working hard and
he's raised a lot of money for MCI, and
they're trying to compete with us from a
technological perspective, from, you
know, getting the product into the
market.
And I wish he would just compete by
building better products.
But I think there's been a lot of
tactics, you know, many, many lawsuits,
all sorts of other crazy stuff out of
this.
And we'll try to just put our head down
and keep working.
Does it make it more difficult to move
from that non-profit model to that for
profit model for open?
We're not moving to a for profit model
where we're not sure we're going to it
all.
But no matter what, the nonprofit will
continue to be extremely important.
It will drive.
The mission will continue to exist.
The board is looking at lots of options
about how to best structure for this
next phase.
But the nonprofit is not changing at
anything or going anywhere.
Okay.
What is your main mission here at the
Paris Action Summit?
Your Stargate?
There's question questions about how
much you're actually going to commit to
that.
Maybe you can give us some numbers on
that, Sam.
What is the messaging here from Unity?
So I've been to an earlier version of
this at Bletchley Park, and that one was
more focused on safety.
This one, people are still talking about
safety.
But but really, I think people are now
saying, okay, this technology is here.
It's having an incredible impact.
We've got to drive it.
There is a lot of questions about how
people can, you know.
Maybe the most common question I've
gotten is can you do a Stargate in my
country?
You know, we need infrastructure here.
We want to do this.
Can you help?
So that that's been a common one.
But a lot of other things about just how
are we going to deploy this technology
to make sure people benefit.
Where's it going to go?
You know, in what ways the model going
to improve.
Last week, we launched this thing called
Deep Research.
We've got a ton of questions about that.
You know, how can we use this to really
drive economic growth?
But maybe economic growth has been the
single biggest theme here.
And having a currency on deep sea can
argue you in the seem to me looking into
that whether they distilled whether they
inappropriately used your your
inferencing data, have you had more
clarity that they did or didn't they get
challenged?
They built a good model.
Many people will distill from many other
models.
Again, I feel so confident about our
research roadmap and also our product
roadmap that, you know, deep sea will do
whatever it is going to do and people do
whatever they're going to do, and we're
just going to try to like build the best
technology we can and get it in people's
hands.
And I think that's mostly going pretty
well.
Do you think Musk's approach then, is
from a position of insecurity about
Excel?
Probably his whole life is from a
position of insecurity.
I feel for the guy who feels that I do,
actually.
I don't think he's like a happy person.
I do feel for him.
Okay.
Do you worry that he has this proximity
to the president and he can influence
the decision making of of the US
presidency and policies around this this
agenda on A.I.
in particular?
Maybe I should, but not particularly.
I mean, I try to just wake up and think
about, like, how we're going to make our
technology better.
Sam Altman, thank you.
Thank you so much, sir.
You're co-founder, of course, of Open
Openai.